<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="rules_activity_title">Rules and Regs.</string>
    <string name="rules_title">Pub Golf Rules and Regulations</string>
    <string name="rules_aim_subtitle">AIM</string>
    <string name="rules_aim_body">To drink one\'s drink in as few sips as possible</string>
    <string name="rules_subtitle">RULES AND REGULATIONS</string>
    <array name="rules_entries">
        <item>Pub Golf is a gentleman/gentlelady\'s game. Decorum shall be maintained throughout. Neither larger-loutism nor association football will be tolerated.</item>
        <item>Golf attire is required on the course. Those not suitably dressed will receive a 2-shot penalty. This includes both hand- and knit-wear.</item>
        <item>Golf is a trusting game. However, all shots must be taken within sight of an impartial umpire (or other player) for score verification. Video evidence may be required in the case of a \'perfect round\'.</item>
        <item>\'Kicking the ball up the course\' through careless drink handling will result in a 3-shot penalty.</item>
        <item>Slow play will be penalised by a 2-shot penalty.</item>
        <item>The golfing party is an inseparable coterie. <b>All</b> players shall play <b>all</b> holes together. There will be no omissions. Latecomers should play the course properly, albeit quickly. Alternatively, they should replicate the preceding holes (in the correct order) at the current hole.</item>
        <item>A \'gimme\' is not defined in pub golf. Those unable to finish a hole will receive a 12 on their scorecard. Get better freshman.</item>
        <item>The rights of water-closet visitation are reserved for players who have completed a hole. \'Irrigating the fairway\' is frowned upon, and testing a hole\'s groundkeeper on the subject is not recommended.</item>
        <item>Spitting has no place on a golf course. Any player who \'re-plays\' a hole will receive a 3-shot penalty.</item>
        <item>\'Shot\' penalties are to be taken as either Tequila or Sambuca shots. Golfers of lesser repute may opt to merely add these shots to their scorecard, but it should be noted that this will invalidate their final score.</item>
        <item>Should further clarification of these rules be required, the course official will clear all ambiguity. They are also responsible for time-keeping and discipline. In the case of the latter, it is on all players to respect and uphold these rules.</item>
    </array>

</resources>